<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Student Association on Marc's Portfolio</title><link>https://marcchen.github.io/tags/student-association/</link><description>Recent content in Student Association on Marc's Portfolio</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 22:32:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://marcchen.github.io/tags/student-association/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>ENSTRAID</title><link>https://marcchen.github.io/posts/ensta/enstraid/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 22:32:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://marcchen.github.io/posts/ensta/enstraid/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="enstraid-transforming-the-future-of-mobility"&gt;ENSTRAID: Transforming the Future of Mobility&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ENSTRAID is an innovative student-led association at ENSTA Paris, focused on retrofitting thermal vehicles into fully electric ones. Our flagship project involves converting a classic Peugeot 205 into a 100% electric vehicle, demonstrating the potential of green energy solutions in the automotive sector. This initiative not only contributes to the ecological transition but also promotes practical engineering experience for students.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As the &lt;strong&gt;Treasurer&lt;/strong&gt; of ENSTRAID during its founding, I oversaw the financial management and ensured that the project stayed within budget while securing necessary funding. We successfully raised &lt;strong&gt;€10,000&lt;/strong&gt;, mainly from ENSTA alumni and IP Paris, which was crucial for moving the project forward.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Technimage</title><link>https://marcchen.github.io/posts/ensta/technimage/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 22:31:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://marcchen.github.io/posts/ensta/technimage/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="technimage---ensta-paris-audiovisual-association"&gt;Technimage - ENSTA Paris Audiovisual Association&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Technimage&lt;/strong&gt; is the audiovisual association of ENSTA Paris. Our mission is to capture and broadcast key moments of the school&amp;rsquo;s student and associative life through various video formats:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Broadcasting the &amp;ldquo;Channels&amp;rdquo;&lt;/strong&gt;: The school&amp;rsquo;s news channel.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Covering associative events&lt;/strong&gt;: Capturing video highlights from association activities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Live productions&lt;/strong&gt;: Live streaming of key events.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Video production&lt;/strong&gt;: Creating clips for the Channel, associations, or the school&amp;rsquo;s communications department.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Short film contests&lt;/strong&gt;: Participating in competitions such as &amp;ldquo;Le Rush,&amp;rdquo; where we won the award for best screenplay at the 5th edition, a 36-hour short film competition.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id="my-contribution"&gt;My Contribution&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As an active member of &lt;strong&gt;Technimage&lt;/strong&gt;, I had the opportunity to edit and produce several video clips, including:&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>