<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Codelab on Marc's Portfolio</title><link>https://marcchen.github.io/posts/codelab/</link><description>Recent content in Codelab on Marc's Portfolio</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 10:52:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://marcchen.github.io/posts/codelab/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Notion2GoogleTask</title><link>https://marcchen.github.io/posts/codelab/notion2googletask/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 10:52:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://marcchen.github.io/posts/codelab/notion2googletask/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="introducing-notion2googletasks-automate-your-task-management-across-platforms">Introducing Notion2GoogleTasks: Automate Your Task Management Across Platforms&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>In today’s fast-paced world, managing your tasks across multiple tools can feel like a juggling act. That’s why I created &lt;strong>Notion2GoogleTasks&lt;/strong>—a powerful microservice that bridges the gap between Notion and Google Tasks, ensuring your task lists are always in sync and up-to-date, no matter which platform you’re using.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Imagine never having to worry about whether your completed tasks in Notion are reflected in Google Tasks, or vice versa. With Notion2GoogleTasks, you get &lt;strong>two-way synchronization&lt;/strong> that works on your schedule—whether you’re using GitHub Actions, cron jobs, or any other runner—so you can focus on what matters most: getting things done.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Bus Countdown Timer</title><link>https://marcchen.github.io/posts/codelab/bus-countdown-timer/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 22:30:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://marcchen.github.io/posts/codelab/bus-countdown-timer/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="bus-station-project-enhancing-public-transport-with-iot">Bus Station Project: Enhancing Public Transport with IoT&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>The &lt;strong>Bus Station Project&lt;/strong> began as a personal solution to a common problem I faced while studying at Paris-Saclay. With only buses to travel between locations, I frequently encountered situations at the Place Marguerite Pery bus station, just in front of Telecom Paris, where no ETA (estimated time of arrival) was available. To know when to leave my house, I had to check the bus schedule on my phone each time before heading out. This sparked the idea to create a system that could provide real-time bus arrival times, making my commute more predictable and efficient.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Gemini Developper Contest</title><link>https://marcchen.github.io/posts/codelab/gemini-developper-contest/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 08:06:25 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://marcchen.github.io/posts/codelab/gemini-developper-contest/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="vision-vendor-a-breakthrough-in-secondhand-market-reselling">Vision Vendor: A Breakthrough in Secondhand Market Reselling&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>As the AI landscape continues to evolve, the &lt;strong>Gemini API Developer Competition by Google&lt;/strong> has become a global stage for developers to showcase their innovations. From June 2024 to August 2024, this competition invited creative minds to harness the power of the &lt;strong>Google Gemini models&lt;/strong> and push the boundaries of AI technology. With up to &lt;strong>$260,000 in prizes&lt;/strong> up for grabs, it attracted a wide range of developers eager to build impactful solutions.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>